builderall.com 2017-06-27

# Builderall - Everything you need to run your business | OMB100, Privacy Policye.

_**Protecting your privacy**_

This privacy policy lets you know how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. When you visit the website and utilize [www.builderall.com](http://www.omb100.com/) you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. In particular, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy.

 _ **Use by minors**_

We do not provide services or sell products or services to minors, or individuals under the age of 18. Persons under 18 years of age may use this website only with a legal guardian or consent of their parents, or by providing legal documentation of their emancipation. Persons under 18 years of age, should not put their personal information in any field or place it anywhere on this website.

 _ **This policy is a part of the  Terms and Conditions of Use**_

This privacy policy is a part of and subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use of this website. You can read these terms in their entirety on the Terms and Conditions of Use page.

 _ **What kind of information we collect**_

As with most websites on the Internet, simply by visiting this website you are giving us some information, including your IP address, the website you visited prior to visiting us, the site you visit when you leave our site, the operating system on your computer, and the browser you used to access our page. Our website automatically saves this basic information about you.

In addition, as most websites do, we may also use cookies. This means that information is transferred from our server to your computer. This information can be used to track your movements and pages visited on our website. Cookies can also be used to customize our content for you. If you use any typical web browser you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and restrict access to your computer in your browser settings.

We may also collect and store all the data you provide to us by entering into the forms on our website or by e-mail; but you still retain the right to choose not to provide any information. However, if you deny providing any fundamental information that we require for access to our products and services, we retain the right to deny access to some or all of the site's features.

Some transactions between you and the website may involve credit cards, debit cards, money orders, and/or third-party payment services. In such transactions, we collect and save information regarding our business relationship with you, including your address, telephone number, and other necessary information. WE DO NOT COLLECT, KEEP or HAVE ACCESS TO ANY INFORMATION ON YOUR CREDIT CARD.

 _ **What we do with your information**_

We use your information for activities necessary to the continuous functionality of the website. For example, you may use your information to contact you about changes on the site, new products and services, promotions, conflict resolution, problem solving, and enforcement of the terms and conditions.

As a general rule, we do not give your information to third parties without your expressed consent. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule described in the following paragraphs.

We may, at our discretion, provide your information to law enforcement or any government officials in the case of fraud investigations, intellectual property infringement, any other illegal activity suspected, or matters that may legally compel us.

Some government intelligence agencies have the technical capacity to access the data on our website without our consent, knowledge, and cooperation. And even if we had knowledge of these intrusions, we do not possess the authority to inform you if pertaining to national security laws. Please keep these risks in mind before providing any information to us or to any other website.

Although we do not disclose any personal identifying information, we may disclose information associated with data about site visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier has to collect your information, you will be notified. You will never be forced to give any information to a third party provider against your will. We restrict the ways outsourced companies use your information in order to protect your privacy. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others.

If we sell this website, we may transfer your information to buyers after the sale is completed. We will not keep your data in our possession.

 _ **DO NOT FOLLOW**_

We try to honor all notices sent by your browser when you visit the BuilderAll website. However, be sure to read the following important information about "interest-based advertising", "remarketing", and "dynamic ads" so you can understand what third party suppliers can do and how you can opt for these scans

 _ **Interest-Based Advertising**_

When you visit our website you may see some advertisements published by us to companies like Google, Bing, Yahoo or other similar entities. When you click on these advertisements companies may collect information about your visit to these websites and use that information to show you compatible or comparable products with which you have expressed an interest.

Our website does not collect or control the advertising and content you see.

To learn more about Google's privacy policies and its DART cookies which generate interest-based advertising, go to [www.google.com/privacy/ads/~~V](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/~~V).

 _ **Protecting your choices**_

If you are using Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, or Google Chrome, you might want to install the extension "protect my choices" on the browser that are using to help keep your opt-out choices.

To learn more, go to [www.aboutads.info/PMC](https://www.aboutads.info/PMC).

 _ **Remarketing**_

This site may use a remarketing tag to advertise online. This means that Google and other third party suppliers can show our ads on the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you based on your previous visits. If you prefer that Google does not use cookies, you should visit "Ad Manager Preferences" at this address [www.google.com/ads/~~number=](https://www.google.com/ads/~~number=).

Alternatively, you can also opt out of the use of third party cookies by going to the opt out page at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

 _ **Dynamic Advertising**_

Our website may use dynamic features of Google ads. To opt for these ads, follow the instructions on [www.support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](http://www.support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en).

If you use any of these sites without opting-out it means that you understand and consent to the collection of information for advertising based on your interests.

 _ **Usernames and Passwords**_

Your access to some parts of our site is protected by a username and password. Do not share your password with anyone. If you enter areas of the site that are password protected please be sure to log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also completely close the browser and reopen it before moving on to other areas on the Internet.

 _ **Commercial information and unsolicited emails**_

If you come across personally identifiable information to another user of our website, you are not authorized to transmit this information to third parties without the consent of the party in question and ours.

We repudiate any unsolicited emails (spam). Information collected on our site, about us or any of our users, is not authorized to be disclosed by you or any other person or sent unsolicited emails or other media to.

 _ **Volunteer Information -  Non-disclosure to suppliers**_

You may not want to leave your personal information open to visitors on your website or third parties who are not our suppliers. Please be very cautious if you do. These third parties have their own privacy policies and behavior that will determine what happens to your information from that point.

 _ **Autoresponders**_

We can use autoresponder emails to communicate with you. To protect your privacy, we use a verification system in opt-in to these communications. You always have the option not to receive these communications by clicking the opt-out link in each message. If you have difficulty opting out, you must send an email to contact@builderall.com

 _ **Policy Changes**_

The terms of this privacy policy may change over time. If any change is made, we will notify you via a public notice on our website. If you disagree with the changes, please contact us. Any changes made to this policy do not apply to information collected before the changes.

It is wise to visit this page and review our privacy policy periodically as you utilize our website.
